Preliminary Inventory of the John M. Bennett Correspondence, 1969-2017 SPEC.RARE.CMS.0171
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
John M. Bennett Correspondence
1969-2017
SPEC.RARE.CMS.0171
Ohio State University Libraries Special Collections
81.98 Cubic feet
As of 2017, John M. Bennet is an American experimental text, sound, and visual poet, active participant in the mail art community, and founder of Luna Bisonte Prods. The John M. Bennett Correspondence contains personal and professional correspondence sent and received by Bennet from 1969-2017, including mail art, poetry, and visual poems.
(104) archival containers; (21) cartons; (2) 5" letter document box; (1) 5" legal document box; (1) 2.5" legal document box; (1) flat box; (1) costume box; (1) oversize folder
Bennett, John M.
Arrangement of Materials
This collection is unprocessed. Materials are arranged in the order received.
Acquisitions Information
RARE.2016.0058: John M. Bennett, 2016 September; RARE.2017.0037: John M. Bennett, 2017 October. RARE.2018.0086: John M. Bennett, 2018 September; Some accessions unknown
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Contains VHS cassettes, compact discs and floppy discs.
Access to Materials
Materials in this collection are available for use, but may be used in the Thompson Library Special Collections reading room only. Audio/visual materials and computer media may need a use copy produced before access is allowed.
Biographical Note
As of 2017, John M. Bennet is an American experimental text, sound, and visual poet and active participant in the mail art community. Through his small press, Luna Bisonte Prods (founded in 1974), he prints small books, chapbooks, cards, pamphlets, artists’ books, audio and video works, and other avant garde works. Bennett was the editor of Lost and Found Times, published by Luna Bisonte Prods, from 1975-2005. Bennett was also curator of the Avant Writing Collection at the Ohio State University Libraries.
Scope and Contents
The John M. Bennett Correspondence contains personal and professional correspondence sent and received by Bennet from 1969-2017, including mail art, poetry, and visual poems. The collection contains correspondence from many avant garde writers and artists, including a large amount of correspondence from visual poets Gyorgy Kostritskii and Jim Leftwich, and correspondence from and about American mail artist and writer Blaster Al Ackerman with whom Bennett collaborated under the joint pen name of Jack A. Withers Smote.
In addition to correspondence, the collection also contains printouts of websites and blogs where Bennett's work appeared, printouts of conversations from internet message boards, compact discs, floppy discs, VHS cassettes, and publications from Luna Bisonte Prods.
Related Materials
SPEC.RARE.CMS.0330
John M. Bennett Correspondence Collection
SPEC.RARE.0184
John M. Bennett and Sheila E. Murphy Correspondence and Collaborations
SPEC.RARE.0185
John M. Bennett and Jim Leftwich Correspondence and Collaboration
SPEC.RARE.0186
John M. Bennett and Davi Det Hompson Papers on Correspondence 1979-1983
SPEC.RARE.0216
John M. Bennett Correspondence with Thomas M. Cassidy (Musicmaster)
Ackerman, Blaster Al, 1939-2013; Bennett, John M.; Leftwich, Jim; Luna Bisonte Prods (Publisher).; Smote, Jack A. Withers; Artists--20th century; Artists--21st century; Mail art; Poets--20th century; Poets--21st century; Small presses--Ohio--Columbus--20th century; Small Presses--Ohio--Columbus--21st century; Visual poetry; Visual poetry--20th century; Visual poetry--21st century
- Correspondence, 1999 March 22-April 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1999 April 16-26 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Correspondence, 1999 April 27-May 4 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1999 may 6-10 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1999 May 11-17 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Correspondence, 1999 May 18-21 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence, 1999 May 24-June 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Correspondence, 1999 June 3-8 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1999 June 10-15 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1999 June 17 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Correspondence, 1999 June 18-July 2 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Correspondence, 1999 July 6-25 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1999 July 16-26 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Correspondence, 1999 July 27-August 26 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Correspondence, 1999 August 27-September 23 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Correspondence, 1999 September 24-28 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Correspondence, 1999 September 30-October 14 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Correspondence, 1999 October 18-November 12 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Correspondence, 1999 November 15-30 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Correspondence received, 1998 October-November 30 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Correspondence received, 1998 November 5-26 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Correspondence received, 1998 November 4-December 1 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Correspondence sent, 1998 November 23-1999 March 18 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Correspondence received, 2000 July 13-September 30 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Correspondence sent, 1999 February-November 23 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Correspondence sent, 1999 November 30-2000 January 1 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Correspondence sent, 2000 January 13-31 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Correspondence sent, 2000 February 1-18 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Correspondence sent, 2000 February 21-March 16 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Correspondence sent, 2000 March 17-April 28 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Correspondence received, 2000 January-March 13 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Correspondence received, 2000 March 14-30 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Correspondence received, 2000 March 31-April 30 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Correspondence received, 1999 March 24-April 16 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Correspondence received, 1999 April 18-26 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Correspondence received, 1999 April 27-May 6 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Correspondence received, 1999 March 24-April 5 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Correspondence received, 1999 April 6-20 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Correspondence received, 1999 April 21-May 2 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Correspondence received, 1999 May 3-9 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Correspondence received, 1999 May 10-19 (Box 7, Folder 41)
- Correspondence received, 1999 May 20-24 (Box 7, Folder 42)
- Correspondence received, 1999 May 25-29 (Box 7, Folder 43)
- Correspondence received, 1999 February 11-March 1 (Box 7, Folder 44)
- Correspondence received, 1999 March 1-12 (Box 7, Folder 45)
- Correspondence received, 1999 March 15-19 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Correspondence received, 1999 January 20-February 15 (Box 7, Folder 47)
- Correspondence received, 1999 February 15-March 2 (Box 7, Folder 48)
- Correspondence received, 1999 May 24-28 (Box 8, Folder 49)
- Correspondence received, 1999 May 29-June 10 (Box 8, Folder 50)
- Correspondence received, 1999 June 11-25 (Box 8, Folder 51)
- Correspondence received, 1999 June 27-July 8 (Box 8, Folder 52)
- Correspondence received, 1999 July 9-19 (Box 8, Folder 53)
- Correspondence received, 1999 July 20-August 6 (Box 8, Folder 54)
- Correspondence received, 1999 August 7-September 14 (Box 8, Folder 55)
- Correspondence received, 1999 September 15-October 2 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Correspondence received, 1999 October 4-14 (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Correspondence received, 1999 October 18-30 (Box 9, Folder 58)
- Correspondence received, 1999 November 1-22 (Box 9, Folder 59)
- Correspondence received, 1999 November 23-December 8 (Box 9, Folder 60)
- Correspondence received, 1999 December 9-2000 December 30 (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Correspondence received, 2000 January 2-February 5 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Correspondence received, 2000 February 7-March 14 (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Correspondence received A, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Correspondence received B, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 65)
- Correspondence received B, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 66)
- Correspondence received B, 1999 (Box 11, Folder 67)
- Correspondence received B, 1992-2003 (Box 11, Folder 68)
- Correspondence received B, circa 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 69)
- Correspondence received B, circa 1995-1999 (Box 12, Folder 70)
- Correspondence received C, 1980-1994 (Box 12, Folder 71)
- Correspondence received C, 1986-2000 (Box 13, Folder 72)
- Correspondence received C, 1997-2001 (Box 13, Folder 73)
- Correspondence received C, 1984-2000 (Box 13, Folder 74)
- Correspondence received D, 1984-1995 (Box 14, Folder 75)
- Correspondence received K, 1977-2000 (Box 14, Folder 76)
- Correspondence received J, 1979-2001 (Box 15, Folder 77)
- Correspondence received I, 1980-2002 (Box 15, Folder 79)
- Correspondence received H, 1987-2001 (Box 15, Folder 80)
- Correspondence received H, 1683-1987 (Box 15, Folder 81)
- Correspondence received H, 1976-1986 (Box 16, Folder 82)
- Correspondence received E, 1979-2001 (Box 16, Folder 83)
- Correspondence received G, 1976-2000 (Box 16, Folder 84)
- Correspondence received G, 1974-1981 (Box 16, Folder 85)
- Correspondence received G, 1981-1986 (Box 17, Folder 86)
- Correspondence received G, 1986-1998 (Box 17, Folder 87)
- Correspondence received F, 1984-1993 (Box 17, Folder 88)
- Correspondence received F, 1979-1996 (Box 18, Folder 89)
- Correspondence received F, 1996-2001 (Box 18, Folder 90)
- Correspondence received L, 1981-1996 (Box 18, Folder 91)
- Correspondence received L, 1977-1984 (Box 18, Folder 92)
- Correspondence received P, 1993-2001 (Box 19, Folder 93)
- Correspondence received P, 1989-2001 (Box 19, Folder 94)
- Correspondence received P, 1993-2000 (Box 19, Folder 95)
- Correspondence received P, 1975-1985 (Box 19, Folder 96)
- Correspondence received P, 1986-1997 (Box 20, Folder 97)
- Correspondence received L, 1985-1992 (Box 20, Folder 98)
- Correspondence received L, 1995-1997 (Box 20, Folder 99)
- Correspondence received L, 1984-1997 (Box 20, Folder 100)
- Correspondence received L, 1996-2000 (Box 21, Folder 101)
- Correspondence received M, 1975-1996 (Box 21, Folder 102)
- Correspondence received M, 1981-1999 (Box 21, Folder 103)
- Correspondence received M, 1983-1998 (Box 22, Folder 104)
- Correspondence received M, 1983-1998 (Box 22, Folder 105)
- Correspondence received M, 1983-1997 (Box 22, Folder 106)
- Correspondence received N, 1984-1998 (Box 22, Folder 107)
- Correspondence received O, 1982-1989 (Box 23, Folder 108)
- Correspondence received R, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 109)
- Correspondence received R, 1981-1984 (Box 23, Folder 110)
- Correspondence received R, 1977-1984 (Box 23, Folder 111)
- Correspondence received R, 1983-2001 (Box 24, Folder 112)
- Correspondence received R, 1986-1989 (Box 24, Folder 113)
- Correspondence received S, 1976-1999 (Box 24, Folder 114)
- Correspondence received S, 1979-1988 (Box 24, Folder 115)
- Correspondence received S, 1983-1986 (Box 25, Folder 116)
- Correspondence received S, 1981-1996 (Box 25, Folder 117)
- Correspondence received S, 1994-1996 (Box 25, Folder 118)
- Correspondence received J and S, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 119)
- Correspondence received Q, 1981-1985 (Box 26, Folder 120)
- Correspondence received T, 1982-2001 (Box 26, Folder 121)
- Correspondence received T, 1982-2000 (Box 26, Folder 122)
- Correspondence received U, 1979-1981 (Box 26, Folder 123)
- Correspondence received V, 1982-1985 (Box 27, Folder 124)
- Correspondence received W, 1977-2000 (Box 27, Folder 125)
- Correspondence received X and Y, 1981-2001 (Box 27, Folder 126)
- Correspondence received A, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 127)
- Correspondence received B, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 128)
- Correspondence received C, 2002 (Box 28, Folder 129)
- Correspondence received D, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 130)
- Correspondence received E, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 131)
- Correspondence received, (F) (Box 29, Folder 132)
- Correspondence received F, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 133)
- Correspondence received F, 2002 (Box 29, Folder 134)
- Correspondence received G, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 135)
- Correspondence received G, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 136)
- Correspondence received H, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 137)
- Correspondence received H, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 138)
- Correspondence received J, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 139)
- Correspondence received K, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 140)
- Correspondence received L, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 141)
- Correspondence received L, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 142)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 November 25-2003 January 2 (Box 32, Folder 143)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 October 22-November 19 (Box 32, Folder 144)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 September 27-2002 October 22 (Box 32, Folder 145)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 September 9-27 (Box 32, Folder 146)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 August 6-November 13 (Box 32, Folder 147)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 June 24-August 5 (Box 32, Folder 148)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 May 9-June 24 (Box 33, Folder 149)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 March 6-May 7 (Box 33, Folder 150)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 March 11-21 (Box 33, Folder 151)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 February 11-March 8 (Box 34, Folder 152)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2002 January 1-February 8 (Box 34, Folder 153)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2001 November 9-2002 January 10 (Box 34, Folder 154)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2001 September 6-November 8 (Box 34, Folder 155)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2001 July 12-September 6 (Box 35, Folder 156)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2001 June 28-July 10 (Box 35, Folder 157)
- Correspondence sent and received, 2001 June 17-26 (Box 35, Folder 158)
- Atlantic Center for the Arts information, undated (Box 35, Folder 159)
- American Center for the Arts information, 2001 May (Box 35, Folder 160)
- Correspondence received, 1994-201 (Box 35, Folder 161)
- Correspondence received, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 162)
- Traproot reviews and drafts, undated (Box 36, Folder 163)
- Correspondence received, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 164)
- Correspondence received M, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 165)
- Correspondence received N, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 166)
- Correspondence received O, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 167)
- Correspondence received P, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 168)
- Correspondence received Q, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 169)
- Correspondence received R, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 170)
- Correspondence received S, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 172)
- Correspondence received T, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 173)
- Correspondence received U, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 174)
- Correspondence received V, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 175)
- Correspondence received W, X, Y and Z, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 176)
- Correspondence received, 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 177a)
- Correspondence received, 2000-2002 (Box 38, Folder 177b)
- Correspondence received from Jim Leftwich, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 178)
- Correspondence received from Jim Leftwich, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 179)
- Correspondence received from Jim Leftwich, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 180)
- Correspondence received from Jim Leftwich, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 181)
- Correspondence received from Jim Leftwich, 2003 (Box 39, Folder 182)
- Correspondence received A, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 183)
- Correspondence received B, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 184)
- Correspondence received C, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 185)
- Correspondence received D, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 186)
- Correspondence received E, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 187)
- Correspondence received F, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 188)
- Correspondence received G, 2003 (Box 42, Folder 189)
- Correspondence received H, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 190)
- Correspondence received H, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 191)
- Correspondence received H, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 192)
- Correspondence received J, 2003 (Box 43, Folder 193)
- Correspondence received J, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 194)
- Correspondence received K, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 195)
- Correspondence received K, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 196)
- Correspondence received L, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 197)
- Correspondence received L, 2003 (Box 44, Folder 198)
- Correspondence received M, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 199)
- Correspondence received M, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 200)
- Correspondence received P and N, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 201)
- Correspondence received P, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 202)
- Correspondence received R, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 203)
- Correspondence received S, 2003 (Box 46, Folder 204)
- Correspondence received S, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 205)
- Correspondence received T, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 206)
- Correspondence received T, 2003 (Box 47, Folder 207)
- Correspondence received X and V, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 208)
- Correspondence received W and B, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 209)
- Correspondence received A, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 210)
- Correspondence received A, 2004 (Box 48, Folder 211)
- Correspondence received B, 2003 (Box 48, Folder 212)
- Correspondence received C, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 213)
- Correspondence received B and C, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 214)
- Correspondence received C and D, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 215)
- Correspondence received E, 2004 (Box 49, Folder 216)
- Correspondence received K, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 217)
- Correspondence received from Al Eaker and BlueMahler@hotmail.com, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 218)
- Correspondence received E, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 219)
- Correspondence received F, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 220)
- Correspondence received F, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 221)
- Correspondence received G, 2004 (Box 50, Folder 222)
- Correspondence received H, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 223)
- Correspondence received H, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 224)
- Correspondence received J, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 225)
- Correspondence received J, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 226)
- Correspondence received K, 2004 (Box 51, Folder 227)
- Correspondence received K, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 228)
- Correspondence received K, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 229)
- Correspondence received K, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 230)
- Correspondence received K, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 231)
- Correspondence received K, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 232)
- Correspondence received K, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 233)
- Correspondence received K and L, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 234)
- Correspondence received (M), 2004 (Box 53, Folder 235)
- Correspondence received M, 2004 (Box 53, Folder 236)
- Correspondence received M, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 237)
- Correspondence received N, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 238)
- Correspondence received O, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 239)
- Correspondence received P, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 240)
- Correspondence received R, 2004 (Box 54, Folder 241)
- Correspondence received R, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 242)
- Correspondence received S, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 243)
- Correspondence received S, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 244)
- Correspondence received S, 2004 (Box 55, Folder 245)
- Correspondence received T, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 246)
- Correspondence received T, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 247)
- Correspondence received V, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 248)
- Correspondence received V, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 249)
- Correspondence received V, 2004 (Box 56, Folder 250)
- Email newsletters from Ben Vautier, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 251-252)
- Correspondence received W, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 253)
- Correspondence from or about Alckerman, 1997-2000 (Box 58, Folder 254)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1986-2000 (Box 58, Folder 255)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1994-1996 (Box 58, Folder 256)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1988-1994 (Box 59, Folder 257)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1992-1995 (Box 59, Folder 258)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1994-1997 (Box 59, Folder 259)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1995-2000 (Box 60, Folder 260)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1988-1990 (Box 60, Folder 261)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1987-1996 (Box 60, Folder 262)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1997-1998 (Box 60, Folder 263)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 263a)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1996-2000 (Box 61, Folder 264)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1996-1999 (Box 61, Folder 265)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1983-1991 (Box 62, Folder 266)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1983 (Box 62, Folder 267)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1983-1985 (Box 62, Folder 268)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1984-1985 (Box 63, Folder 269)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1980-1992 (Box 63, Folder 270)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1981-1988, circa 2000s (Box 63, Folder 271)
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Compact discs; approximate run time: unknown
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 272)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1976, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 273)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1988-1990 (Box 64, Folder 274)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1984-1989 (Box 65, Folder 275)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1981-1986 (Box 65, Folder 276)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1985-1991 (Box 65, Folder 277)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1985-1987 (Box 66, Folder 278)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1982-1989 (Box 66, Folder 279)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1981-1985 (Box 66, Folder 280)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1982-1984 (Box 66, Folder 281)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1983-1985 (Box 67, Folder 282)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1982-1985 (Box 67, Folder 283)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 284)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1983-2002 (Box 68, Folder 285)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 286)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 287)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 288)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 289)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 2002 (Box 69, Folder 290)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 2000-2001 (Box 69, Folder 291)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 2000-2001 (Box 70, Folder 292)
- Correspondence from or about Al Ackerman, 1998 (Box 70, Folder 293)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, undated (Box 71, Folder 294)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 295)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2004 (Box 71, Folder 296)
- Artwork from Gyorgy Kostriskii, circa 2003 (Box 72, Folder 297)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 298)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2003 (Box 72, Folder 299)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 300)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 301)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2003 (Box 73, Folder 302)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 303)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 304)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostritskii, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 305)
- Correspondencefrom Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 306)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostriskii, 2003 (Box 75, Folder 307)
- Correspondence from Jim Leftwich, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 308)
- Correspondence from Jim Leftwich, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 309)
- Correspondence from Jim Leftwich, 2004 (Box 76, Folder 310)
- Correspondence from Jim Leftwich, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 311)
- Correspondence from Jim Leftwich, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 312a)
- Correspondence from Jim Leftwich, 2004 (Box 77, Folder 312b)
- Website files, undated (Box 78, Folder 312c)
- Website files, undated (Box 78, Folder 312d)
- Website files, undated (Box 78, Folder 312e)
- Website files, undated (Box 78, Folder 312f)
- Website files, undated (Box 78, Folder 312g)
  Floppy disks
- Correspondence received, 1982-2004 (Box 79)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostritskii (Box 80)
- Correspondence from Gyorgy Kostritskii, undated (Box 81)
- Correspondence received A, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 313)
- Correspondence received A, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 314)
- Correspondence received B, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 315)
- Correspondence received B, 2005 (Box 82, Folder 316)